Wassim El Haddaoui (+46) 73 71 99 337

- Elhaddaouiwassim@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/wassim-el-haddaoui/
- https://simoportfolio.com/ https://github.com/CallMeSimo

Summary - For the impatient

I am an experienced software developer with a focus on creating efficient and effective solutions. Through my career, I have honed my skills in optimizing strategies, responsive design, and website analytics. I have successfully tackled complex hardware, software, and network issues, consistently demonstrating my problem-solving abilities. With a degree in Information and Media Technology, I have completed impactful IoT projects and gained experience leading workshops, highlighting my leadership and communication skills. Fluent in both Swedish and English, I possess excellent communication abilities essential for collaborating effectively with diverse teams.

EXPERIENCE

Technician, Stena Recycling AB, Halmstad, Sweden, Oct 2022 - Present

- Manage and configure servers, drive enclosures, switches, desktops, and laptops
- Test and resolve basic issues related to networking equipment
- Manage network configurations and set up new devices

Developer, ASSA ABLOY Entrance System (Internship), Landskrona, Sweden, Mar 2022 - Apr 2022

- Guided and assigned tasks to a 3-person collaboration project
- Organized meetings to solve communication issues between devices
- Divided responsibilities for creating HMI between designer and programmer
- Operated complex hardware, software, and network problems and prepared reports summarizing and analyzing the issues
- Developed technical skills in PLC programming and HMI development
- Collaborated on automation projects involving industrial control systems

WordPress Developer, MADPromotions (Internship), Birkirkara, Malta, Apr 2022 - May 2022

- Conducted site audits and implemented optimization strategies for improved site speed and SEO
- Developed responsive designs and mobile-first solutions
- Utilized website analytics tools, such as Google Analytics
- Demonstrated excellent problem-solving and debugging skills

EDUCATION

Nordens Tekniska Institut, Informations- och medieteknik, Aug 2018 - Jun 2021

- Learned web and software development fundamentals
- Completed IoT projects using temperature sensors, light sensors, motors, etc.

Nordens Tekniska Institut, Software development Gymnasieingenjör, Aug 2021 - Jun 2022

- Led several workshops as a team leader
- In-dept software development with focus in web development.

SKILLS

Software Development	Web Development	Problem Solving	Optimization Strategies
Communication	HMI Development	Leadership	PLC Programming
Industrial Control Systems	Database Management	Data Analysis	Team Collaboration